PARASKEVOPOULOS PANAGIOTIS

Tel: +306992466273 / E-mail: takisparas23@gmail.com

Address: Mpizaniou 27, Chalandri, 15232, Athens, Greece.

DoB: 18/10/1996

PERSONAL SUMMARY

I'm a new enthusiastic junior web developer interested in both front-end and back-end development. I always love to work in teams as I have 6 years of experience in Wind company as a telecommunication manager. I'm a fast learner and I like new challenges and goals as I expand my knowledge and my coding skills through them.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: Javascript, Java, Python, PHP, HTML, CSS, SQL

 Technologies: RESTful Web Services, jQuery,Bootstrap, Angular.js, Springboot, Django

Operating Systems: Windows, Linux

PROJECTS

Project Details	Technologies	Description
Client: MINISTRY OF DIGITAL GOVERNANCE Project: Creating the official site	Java Springboot, SQL, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Angular, JQuery, Node.js, Git Hibernate, Postman, Api key Authorization	Internship at the ministry on the development of the official website as well as its optimization on national security issues
Client: Xarokopeio university Project: Thesis	Python, Django, Php,Windows PowerShell,CSS, PostgreSql	Development of an online application for thesis management. Also interaction with students as well as the secretariat to facilitate the process

Client: Xarokopeio university Project: Feeding application management system	Java Springboot Angular,Mysql, Maven, Intelij, Visual Studio, Rest Api	Creating a web application for students, where the students can enter the application site and have the opportunity to make their applies and also see their ranking order (only their own) and whether they ultimately entitled to free meals or not, once the process is completed.
Client: Xarokopeio university Project: E-shop	HTML, Css,Php	University Project of creating an online e-shop selling food products.

WORK EXPERIENCE

14/9/2014 – present: I work on individual website creation projects.

1/8/2014 – 11/8/2021: Team manager at the Wind company in telecommunications matters.

1/7/2019 - 30/9/2019: University Practise at Ministry of Digital Government

8/8/2019 – present : Basketball coach as secondary job.

EDUCATION

2014-2021

Xarokopeio University of informatics and telematics, Greece.

Thesis Title: Development of an web application for the management of diplomatic theses of the Harokopio University.

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Greek (Native), English (B2 level, fluent in reading, writing and speaking)